Frank E. Fowle Collection MS089
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Playscripts, 1852 -- 1969; 1880 -- 1920; MS089.001; 5.05 Linear Feet
  - Published playscripts, 1852 -- 1969; MS089.001.002
    - The Scarlet Letter, 1871; MS089.001.024.00026; Andrews, George H. (Box 24)
    - School, MS089.001.024.00027; Robertson, T.W. (Box 24)
    - The School for Scheming, MS089.001.024.00028; Boucicault, Dion (Box 24)
    - A Scrap of Paper, MS089.001.024.00029; Simpson, J. Palgrave (Box 24)
    - A Sea of Troubles, 1894; MS089.001.024.00030; Baker, George M. (Box 24)
    - The Serious Family, MS089.001.024.00031; Barnett, Morris (Box 24)
    - Shaughraun, MS089.001.024.00032; Boucicault, Dion (Box 24)
    - Silas Marner, 1915; MS089.001.024.00033; Owen, Franklin S. (Box 24)
    - Silverstone's Wager, MS089.001.024.00034; Andrews, R.R. (Box 24)
    - The Skeleton in the Closet, 1930; MS089.001.024.00035; Worthington, William; Twist, John Stuart (Box 24)
    - Slasher and Crasher, MS089.001.024.00036; Morton, J.M. (Box 24)
    - Slave Life, or Uncle Tom's Cabin, MS089.001.024.00037; Lemon, Mark; Taylor, Tom (Box 24)
    - Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs, 1925; MS089.001.024.00038; White, Jesse Braham (Box 24)
    - So It's Christmas Again, 1956; MS089.001.024.00039; Asbrand, Karin (Box 24)
      A Christmas play for the Grades.
    - Society, MS089.001.024.00040; Robertson, T.W. (Box 24)
    - Sparks Divine, 1920; MS089.001.024.00041; Breene, Bessie Springer (Box 24)
    - Special Performances, MS089.001.024.00042; Harrison, Wilmot (Box 24)
    - Special Pleading, 1921; MS089.001.024.00043; Duffy, Bernard (Box 24)
    - The Stranger, MS089.001.024.00044; Von Kotzebue, A. F.F. (Box 24)
    - Stung, 1925; MS089.001.024.00045; Walker, Lydia, LeBaron (Box 24)
    - Stupid Cupid, 1896; MS089.001.024.00046; Rawley, Bert C. (Box 24)
    - Sunset, MS089.001.024.00047; Jerome, K.J. (Box 24)
    - Sun-Up, 1924; MS089.001.024.00048; Vollmer, Lula (Box 24)
    - Sweethearts, MS089.001.024.00049; Gilbert, W.S. (Box 24)
    - Sylvia, MS089.001.024.00050; Rhys-Herbert, W.; Inch, Maude Elizabeth (Box 24)
    - Take That Girl Away, MS089.001.024.00051; Buckingham, L.S. (Box 24)
    - Taming a Tiger, MS089.001.024.00052 (Box 24)
    - Taming a Truant, MS089.001.024.00053; Wigan, Horace (Box 24)
    - Team-Work, 1912; MS089.001.024.00054; Gott, Charles; Gallupe, Harold Quimby (Box 24)
    - The Ticket of Leave Man, MS089.001.024.00055; Taylor, Tom (Box 24)
    - A Thief in the House, 1909; MS089.001.024.00056; Robinson, R.M. (Box 24)
    - Their Wife, 1913; MS089.001.024.00057; Middleton, George (Box 24)
    - The Third Man, 1915; MS089.001.024.00058; Benedix, Roderich (Box 24)
    - Time and the Hour, MS089.001.024.00059; Dale, Felix; Palgrave, Simpson J. (Box 24)
    - Tom Cobb, 1915; MS089.001.024.00060; Gilbert, W.S. (Box 24)
    - Tradition, 1914; MS089.001.024.00061; Middleton, George (Box 24)
    - Tricks of the Trade, 1899; MS089.001.024.00062; Latour, Eugene (Box 24)
    - Trifles, 1916; MS089.001.024.00063; Glaspell, Susan (Box 24)
    - The Trustee, 1891; MS089.001.024.00064; Browne, W.M. (Box 24)
    - Truth, 1908; MS089.001.024.00065; Fezandie, Clement (Box 24)
    - Trying It On, MS089.001.024.00066; Brough, William (Box 24)
    - Turkish Bath, MS089.001.024.00067; Burnand, F.C.; Williams, Montagu (Box 24)
    - Turned Up, MS089.001.024.00068; Melford, Mark (Box 24)
    - Turning the Tables, MS089.001.024.00069; Poole, John (Box 24)
    - Twelfth Night, 1913; MS089.001.024.00070; Shakespeare, William (Box 24)
      An acting edition as produced by Granville Barker.
    - Twenty Minutes Under an Umbrella, MS089.001.024.00071; Dubourg, A.W. (Box 24)
    - The Two Buzzards, 1888; MS089.001.024.00072; Morton, J.M. (Box 24)
    - Two Can Play at That Game, MS089.001.024.00073; Lafferriere, Adolphe; Pierron, Eugene (Box 24)
    - Two Gay Deceivers, MS089.001.024.00074; Lacy, T.H.; Robertson, W. (Box 24)
    - Two Gentlemen in a Fix, MS089.001.024.00075; Suter, W.E. (Box 24)
    - The Two Orphans, MS089.001.024.00076 (Box 24)
      Printed not published.
    - The Two Puddifoots, 1870; MS089.001.024.00077; Morton, J.M. (Box 24)
    - Two Veterans, 1899; MS089.001.024.00078; Hageman, Maurice (Box 24)
    - Uncle, 1905; MS089.001.024.00079; Byron, H. J. (Box 24)
    - Uncle Tom's Cabin, MS089.001.024.00080; Aiken, George L. (Box 24)
    - Uncle's Will, 1910; MS089.001.024.00081; Smith, S. Theyre (Box 24)
    - Valley Farm, MS089.001.024.00082 (Box 24)
    - Venice Preserved, MS089.001.024.00083; Otway, Thomas (Box 24)
    - The Voice of Authority, 1912; MS089.001.024.00084; Porter, Bertha Currier (Box 24)
    - Waiting, 1913; MS089.001.024.00085; Middleton, George (Box 24)
    - Wanted, A Male Cook, 1876 -- 1894; MS089.001.024.00086; Baker, George M. (Box 24)
    - War to the Knife, MS089.001.024.00087; Byron, Henry J. (Box 24)
    - Watchfires, 1917; MS089.001.024.00088; Mygatt, Tracy D. (Box 24)
    - Waterloo, 1907; MS089.001.024.00089; Conan Doyle, Sir Arthur (Box 24)
    - Weak Women, MS089.001.024.00090; Byron, Henry J. (Box 24)
    - The Wedding Feast, 1896; MS089.001.024.00091; Leahy, W.A. (Box 24)
    - West End or the Irish Heiress, MS089.001.024.00092; Boucicault, Dion (Box 24)
    - Who is Who, MS089.001.024.00093; WIlliams, Thomas (Box 24)
    - Who's Your Friend, MS089.001.024.00094; Planche, J.R. (Box 24)
    - The Wife: A Tale of Mantau, MS089.001.024.00095; Knowles, James Sheridan (Box 24)
    - Wild Oats, MS089.001.024.00096; O'Keefe, John (Box 24)
    - The Willow Copse, 1855; MS089.001.024.00097; Boucicault, Dion (Box 24)
    - The Winter's Tale, 1913; MS089.001.024.00098; Shakespeare, William (Box 24)
      Acting edition as produced by Granville Barker.
    - Witches' Brew, 1956; MS089.001.024.00099; Asbrand, Karin (Box 24)
    - A Woman of No Importance, 1906; MS089.001.024.00100; Wilde, Oscar (Box 24)
    - The Wonder, MS089.001.024.00101; Centlivre, Susanna (Box 24)
    - Woodcock's Little Game, MS089.001.024.00102; Morton, J.M. (Box 24)
    - The Would-Be Invalid, 1950; MS089.001.024.00103; Moliere (Box 24)
    - Yellow Roses, MS089.001.024.00104; Young, Sir Charles L. (Box 24)
    - Young Mrs. Winthrop, 1899; MS089.001.024.00105; Howard, Bronson (Box 24)
    - The Zone Police, 1914; MS089.001.024.00106; Davies, R.H. (Box 24)
  - Catalogue of plays and inventory of scrapbooks, 1902; MS089.001.025.001 (Box 25)
    Two books with Fowle's handwritten notes, one a catalogue of plays found in his collection (see boxes 22-24) and one lists, by actor, where clippings can be found in his scrapbook collection (see boxes 1-19).
- Playbills, 1881 -- 1980; 1910 -- 1939; MS089.002; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains playbills from amateur productions that Fowle directed or was involved with in the Boston area, mostly Malden and Winchester.
  This series is arranged chronologically by year.
  - Dancecard, 1881; MS089.002.020.00115 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1885; MS089.002.020.00116 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1886; MS089.002.020.00117 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1888; MS089.002.020.00118 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1890; MS089.002.020.00119 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1891; MS089.002.020.00120 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1892; MS089.002.020.00121 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1897; MS089.002.020.00122 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1898; MS089.002.020.00123 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1899; MS089.002.020.00124 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1900; MS089.002.020.00125 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1901; MS089.002.020.00126 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1902; MS089.002.020.00127 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1903; MS089.002.020.00128 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1904; MS089.002.020.00129 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1905; MS089.002.020.00130 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1906; MS089.002.020.00131 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1907; MS089.002.020.00132 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1908; MS089.002.020.00133 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1909; MS089.002.020.00134 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1910; MS089.002.020.00135 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1911; MS089.002.020.00136 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1912; MS089.002.020.00137 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1913; MS089.002.020.00138 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1914; MS089.002.020.00139 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1915; MS089.002.020.00140 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1916; MS089.002.020.00141 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1917; MS089.002.020.00142 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1918; MS089.002.020.00143 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1919; MS089.002.020.00144 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1920; MS089.002.020.00145 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1921; MS089.002.020.00146 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1922; MS089.002.020.00147 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1923; MS089.002.020.00148 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1924; MS089.002.020.00149 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1925; MS089.002.020.00150 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1926; MS089.002.020.00151 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1927; MS089.002.020.00152 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1928; MS089.002.020.00153 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1929; MS089.002.020.00154 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1930; MS089.002.020.00155 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1931; MS089.002.020.00156 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1932; MS089.002.020.00157 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1933; MS089.002.020.00158 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1934; MS089.002.020.00159 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1935; MS089.002.020.00160 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1936; MS089.002.020.00161 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1937; MS089.002.020.00162 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1938; MS089.002.020.00163 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, 1939; MS089.002.020.00164 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, The Players, 1918 -- 1937; MS089.002.020.00165 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, Old Belfry Club, 1928; MS089.002.020.00166 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbills, MS089.002.020.00167 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Playbill, 1980; MS089.002.020.00168 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
    American Repertory Theatre's production of A Midsummer Night's Dream.
  - Various playbills collected by Fowle, local productions, 1908 -- 1939; MS089.002.020.00169 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
- Scrapbooks, 1880 -- 1940; 1883 -- 1930; MS089.003; 8.55 Linear Feet
  This series includes scrapbooks of theatrical productions in the Boston area from 1883-1930.
  This series is arranged as found.
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 1, 1883 -- 1895; MS089.003.001.001 (Box 1)
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 2, 1880 -- 1900; MS089.003.002.001 (Box 2)
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volumes 3 and 4, 1891 -- 1904; MS089.003.003.001 (Box 3)
    Vol. 3 (1900-04). Vol. 4 (1891-99).
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 5, 1899 -- 1905; MS089.003.004.001 (Box 4)
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 6, 1903 -- 1908; MS089.003.005.001 (Box 5)
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 7, 1905 -- 1912; MS089.003.006.001 (Box 6)
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 8, 1908 -- 1911; MS089.003.007.001 (Box 7)
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 9, 1909 -- 1914; MS089.003.008.001 (Box 8)
    Newspaper clippings, photos, programs, and misc. memorabilia
    Scrapbook; Fowle, Frank E.
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 10, 1911 -- 1913; MS089.003.009.001 (Box 9)
    Newspaper clippings and announcements.
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 11 - local and college theatrical productions, 1912 -- 1921; MS089.003.010.001 (Box 10)
    Clippings and playbills of productions Fowle was involved with.
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 12, 1914 -- 1917; MS089.003.011.001 (Box 11)
    Newspaper clippings, photos, programs, and misc. memorabilia.
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 13, 1917 -- 1920; MS089.003.012.001 (Box 12)
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 14, 1920 -- 1923; MS089.003.013.001 (Box 13)
    Newsclippings, photos, programs, and misc. memorabilia.
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 16, 1924 -- 1927; MS089.003.014.001 (Box 14)
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 17, 1927 -- 1930; MS089.003.015.001 (Box 15)
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 18, 1910 -- 1935; MS089.003.016.001 (Box 16)
    Includes playbills, clippings and some letters.
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 19, 1908 -- 1940; MS089.003.017.001 (Box 17)
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 20(?), 1937 -- 1940; MS089.003.018.001 (Box 18)
    Newspaper clippings, programs, and misc. memorabilia.
  - Theatre clippings scrapbook, 1895; MS089.003.019.001 (Box 19)
    Includes clippings on productions, obituaries, reviews of dramatic seasons in Boston, and recollections of famous actors.
  - Theatre Scrapbook, volume 15, 1921 -- 1928; MS089.003.026.00001 (Box 26)
- Production notes, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains Fowle's hand written and typewritten notes on productions he worked on including notes on costumes, blocking, props lists, scene break downs, and character break downs.
  - Stop Thief, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00001 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Two Orphans, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00002 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Stung, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00003 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Only 38, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00004 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - A Pair of Sixes, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00005 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Mice and Men, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00006 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Billeted, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00007 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Queen's Husband, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00008 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - What Every Woman Knows, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00009 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Charley's Aunt, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00010 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Curtain Rises, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00011 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Her Husband's Wife, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00012 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Nothing But the Truth, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00013 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Post Road, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00014 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Bachelor Road, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00015 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Meet the Wife, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00016 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Grumpy, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00017 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Green Stockings, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00018 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Double Door, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00019 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - This Woman Business, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00020 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Esmerelda, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00021 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Sport of Kings, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00022 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Wedding Bells, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00023 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Partners for Life, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00024 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Famous Mrs. Fair, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00025 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Disraeli, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00026 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Fickle Fortune, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00027 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Captain Applejack, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00028 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - You and I, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00029 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Snowball, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00030 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Arrival of Kitty, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00031 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Rebellious Jane, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00032 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Miss Somebody Else, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00033 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Patty Makes Things Hum, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00034 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Guvinor, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00035 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Magistrate, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00036 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - When a Man Married, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00037 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Our Town, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00038 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Dulcy, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00039 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Lion and the Mouse, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00040 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Led Astray, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00041 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Hoodoo, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00042 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The District Attorney, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00043 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Dead of the Night, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00044 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - As Husbands Go, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00045 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Her Master's Voice, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00046 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Engaged, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00047 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Loyalties, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00048 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Amazons, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00049 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Nicholas Nickleby, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00050 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Mrs. Bupstead-Leigh, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00051 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - A Christmas Carol, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00052 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Chuzzlewits, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00053 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - A Successful Calamity, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00054 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Davidson Case, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00055 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Late Christopher Bean, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00056 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - You Can't Take it With You, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00057 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Adam and Eva, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00058 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Davidson Case, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00059 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Dandy Dick, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00060 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Sun-Up, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00061 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Hawk Island, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00062 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Rivals, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00064 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - A Scrap of Paper, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00065 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Old Lady 31, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00066 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Old Homestead, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00067 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Holiday, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00068 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Bad Man, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00069 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Haunted House, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00070 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Three Wise Fools, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00071 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Showoff, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00072 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Seven Keys to Baldplate, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00073 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Alias the Deacon, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00074 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Dolly Reforming Herself, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00075 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Captain Kidd, Jr., 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00076 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Man Who Stayed at Home, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00077 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - One of the Family, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00078 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - At Mrs. Beams, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00079 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Thank You, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00080 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Bird in Hand, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00081 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Monsieur de Beaufort, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00082 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - On the Hiring Line, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00083 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Daisy Farm, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00084 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Nevada, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00085 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Tailor's Son, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00086 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Box and Cox, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00087 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Voice of Authority, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00088 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Our Boys, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00089 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Cozy Couple, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00090 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Under Cover, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00091 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Eliza Come to Sky, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00092 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The New Lady Bantock, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00093 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Six Cylinder Love, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00094 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - A Prince There Was, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00095 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Constantine Pueblo Jone, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00096 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Japanese Girl, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00097 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Second Puncture, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00098 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - All-of-a-Sudden Peggy, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00099 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - New Brooms, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00100 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - So This is London, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00101 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Intimate Strangers, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00102 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Tavern, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00103 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Peg O' my Heart, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00104 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Tommy, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00105 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Patsy, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00106 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00107 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Whole Town's Talking, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00108 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - The Misleading Lady, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00110 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Minick, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00111 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Applesauce, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00112 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Enchanted April, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00113 (Box MS089 Shared 1)
  - Various Notes on Productions, 1915 -- 1930; MS089.004.020.00114 (Box MS089 Shared 1)